John Gordos

720-212-8404

john.gordos@outlook.com

12507 W. Alameda Dr. Lakewood, CO 80228

SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS

Curious, self-starter who values making things easy and more efficient for people by applying back-end web development knowledge to help maintain systems and implement scalable solutions. Proficient at building routes with Express is to support site navigation, transacting with a database, and other back-end services. Strong ability to model data from having a total of 5+ years of experience as a Salesforce administrator. Advanced knowledge of the Salesforce platform with a strong desire to branch out and learn more technologies.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

JavaScript ES6+, HTML5, jQuery, React, Node, MongoDB, Mongoose, MySQL, Sequelize, Express, Handlebars, Git, GitHub, Salesforce Platform, Salesforce Apex, Salesforce Lightning Web Components, Salesforce Flows

WORK EXPERIENCE

Tipico US

Salesforce Developer

March 2022 – May 2023

- As the only developer, implemented a domain-service framework with apex that helps enforce SOLID principles and allow future developers to implement unit testing with Salesforce's Stub API
- Used Atlassian Confluence to write documentation describing patterns, maintenance, new user setup, and the deployment process.
- Built an integration between Salesforce and Slack that would alert support managers of events related to chats – like if a chat was waiting in the queue for several minutes or if no agents were online.
- Created custom endpoints in order to periodically receive data from MySQL databases through AWS.
- Administrated PhoneIQ, which had a CTI with Salesforce that ensured our customer's calls were routed to the relevant agent and that the agent can complete post-call actions.
- Managed all Salesforce users, including new user setup and transitions.

Evolve Vacation Rental

Salesforce Developer

March 2020 – August 2021

- Migrated Salesforce components into unlocked packages to better organize the database and its automations, frequently reworking existing code to run more efficiently and respect our new patterns.
- Collaborated with project managers to refactor a homeowner onboarding application, which reduced the time it took to complete and allowed applicants to start from where they left off.
- Coordinated with Dell Boomi developers to help build an integration with Avalara, allowing users to essentially upsert tax data to Salesforce.
- Facilitated deployments by leading meetings to confirm which stories would be deployed, deployed work created by other developers, monitored exceptions, and performed initial troubleshooting.

Wide Open West

Salesforce Administrator

October 2018 – March 2020

- Debugged and helped redesign apex triggers to respect Salesforce governor limits and run more efficiently, resulting in faster transactions and improved data quality.
- Created and organized solution design documents, admin training materials, and summaries of components.
- Advocated for code review with contractors to ensure best practices were followed, acceptance criteria were met, and code ran efficiently.
- Administered Docusign's integration with Salesforce, allowing the sales department to send contracts to customers from within Salesforce.
- Used ServiceNow to provide technical support for Salesforce, its integrations, and Docusign.
- Collaborated with stakeholders to define solutions and implemented them using apex and flows.

Awards/Acknowledgements

Received the Business Impact Award from Wide Open West for my hard work, devotion, and commitment to excellence.

Return Path

Salesforce Support Specialist

May 2015 – April 2017

- Provided business and technical support for Salesforce users from various departments using Salesforce Service Cloud.
- Setup new users and managed profiles, permission sets, and roles for existing users.
- Participated in SCRUM ceremonies to prioritize and design enhancements.
- Created and modified Salesforce automations and reports to streamline the flow of data and present it in a meaningful way.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF DENVER (Denver, Colorado) Full-Stack Coding Bootcamp	May 2023
UNIVERSITY OF COLORADO DENVER (Denver, Colorado) Bachelor of Science: Mathematics	May 2015 GPA: 3.6

CERTIFICATIONS

Salesforce Certified Administrator	October 2015
Salesforce Certified Advanced Administrator	February 2018
Salesforce Certified Platform Developer I	December 2019